Guide to the Royal Cortissoz Papers
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Cortissoz Correspondence and Manuscripts, 1864-1959; Series I; 5.04; (12 boxes)
  - James, Henry, William, and Alec, 1944-46 (Box 6, Folder 259)
  - James, Henry, 1899-1900 (Box 6, Folder 260-261)
  - Jay, John, 1878 (Box 6, Folder 262)
  - Jewett, Sarah Orne, n.d. (Box 6, Folder 263)
  - Johnson, Robert Underwood, 1924-31 (Box 6, Folder 264)
  - Jones, Mary Cadwalader, 1929 (Box 6, Folder 265)
  - "K" general, 1919, n.d. (Box 7, Folder 266-267)
    Karplus, Greta
    Keen, Herbert B.
    Kelekian, Dikran G.
    Kelland, Clarence Budington
    Kemp, Edward C.
    Kennedy, Mitchell
    Kent, Rockwell
    Keppel, David
    Kimball, Alonzo
    Kimball, Fiske
    Kimball, Lydia
    Kimbrich, F.B.
    King, Molly
    Kipling, Rudyard
    Kleinberger, F.
    Knoedler, Roland
    Konrad, P.G.
    Kronberg, Louis
  - Keller, Deane, 1932 (Box 7, Folder 268)
  - Kelsey, Albert, 1923-41 (Box 7, Folder 269)
  - Kendall, William Mitchell, 1922, n.d. (Box 7, Folder 270)
  - Kendall, William Sergeant, 1938, n.d. (Box 7, Folder 271)
  - Kent, H.W., 1913-45 (Box 7, Folder 272)
  - Kinney, Troy, 1920-29 (Box 7, Folder 273)
  - Kirby, Rollin, 1928-39 (Box 7, Folder 274)
  - Kirby, Thomas E., 1922-23 (Box 7, Folder 275)
  - Krehbiel, H., 1922-23, n.d. (Box 7, Folder 276)
  - Kress, Samuel H., 1939 (Box 7, Folder 277)
  - "L" general, 1913-53 (Box 7, Folder 278-280)
    Lamb, Charles Rollinson
    Lane, James W.
    Lang, A.
    Langdon, William Chauncy
    Lawrie, Lee
    Leffingwell, R.C.
    Leon, Paul
    Lerolle, G.
    Lever, Hayley
    Levi, Julian Clarence
    Lewisohn, Sam A.
    Lichtenauer, Rbecca D.
    Lincoln, James Otis
    Ligne, Prince de
    "Lindy"
    Lippmann, Walter
    Litchfield, Electus D.
    Littell, Robert
    Lloyd, Finley Hall, Mrs.
    Lodge, J.E.
    Loomis, Battell
    Lothrop, M.B., Miss
    Lober, Georg
    Low, Benjamin R.C.
    Low, Edward F.
    Lyman, Hart
  - La Farge, John (Sketchbook), n.d. (Box 7, Folder 281)
  - La Farge, John Papers (notes, memoranda...), 1906 (Box 7, Folder 282-285)
  - La Farge, John, 1901-1910, n.d. (Box 7, Folder 286-289)
  - La Farge, Bancel, 1911 (Box 7, Folder 290)
  - La Farge (Family), 1911-44, n.d. (Box 7, Folder 291)
  - Lane, James W. (letter from Cortissoz), 1941-53 (Box 8, Folder 292)
  - Lambotte, Paul, 1916-27 (Box 8, Folder 293)
  - Lamont, Thomas W., 1942-45 (Box 8, Folder 294)
  - Lay, Charles Downing, 1944 (Box 8, Folder 295)
  - Leland, Charles Godfrey, 1896-1902 (Box 8, Folder 296)
  - Lemordant, Jean Julien, 1919, n.d. (Box 8, Folder 297)
  - Lie, Jonas, 1926-35 (Box 8, Folder 298)
  - Lindeberg, H.T., 1910-15, n.d. (Box 8, Folder 299)
  - Lodge, Henry C., 1921-48 (Box 8, Folder 300)
  - Low, Will H., 1919-32 (Box 8, Folder 301)
  - "M" general, 1882-53, n.d. (Box 8, Folder 302-306)
    MacDonald, Charles Blair
    Mackay, Billy
    Macy, Nelson
    Magafan, Jenne
    Mallett, Arthur
    Malone, Robert James
    Mansfield, Burton
    Mansfield, Howard
    Manship, Paul
    March, Edward
    Margrand, Allan
    Marquand, Henry
    Mase, George
    Mason, M.
    Masson, Thomas L.
    Mastai, Boleslaw
    Mauri, Adele
    Maynard, Louis
    McCorman, Francis
    McCormick, William B.
    McDermott, John Francis
    McGuire, William J.
    McKee, Oliver
    Meader, Marguerite R.
    Mechlin, Leila
    Meloney, William Brown, Mrs.
    Mencken, H.B.
    Merrill, Bradford
    Merryman, R.S.
    Millier, Arthur
    Mills, Ogden, Mrs.
    "Missy"
    Montross, N.E.
    Moore, Charles H.
    Morgan, John Hill
    Morris, Benjamin Wistar
    Morris, Bingham Willing
    Morse, E.W.
    Moses, Lionel
    Mowbrey-Clarke, John
    Murphy, Adam Clifford
  - MacBeth, William, 1919-31 (Box 8, Folder 307)
  - Mackay, Clarence, 1923-53 (Box 8, Folder 308-312)
  - Magonigle, Harold Van Buren, 1909-28 (Box 8, Folder 313)
  - Marshall, Henry Rutgers, 1922 (Box 8, Folder 314)
  - Mather, Frank Jewett, 1906-44 (Box 8, Folder 315)
  - Matthews, Brander, 1914-22 (Box 8, Folder 316)
  - Matthews, Gladys, 1922-48 (Box 8, Folder 317)
  - McCutcheon, George Barr, 1922-27 (Box 8, Folder 318)
  - McKim, Charles F., 1905 (Box 8, Folder 319)
  - Mead, William R., 1922-25 (Box 8, Folder 320)
  - Melchers, Gari, 1921-54 (Box 8, Folder 321)
  - Mellon, A.W., 1937 (Box 8, Folder 322)
  - Meyer, Herbert, 1932-41, n.d. (Box 8, Folder 323)
  - Miller, Alice (Duer), n.d. (Box 8, Folder 324)
  - Milles, Carl, 1932, n.d. (Box 8, Folder 325)
  - Millet, J.B., 1924-34, n.d. (Box 8, Folder 326)
  - Milne, A.A., n.d. (Box 8, Folder 327)
  - Moe, Henry Allen, 1942-52 (Box 8, Folder 328)
  - Montgomery, John F., 1918-53 (Box 8, Folder 329)
  - Moore, Charles, 1922-42 (Box 8, Folder 330)
  - Moore, George, 1898-1902 (Box 8, Folder 331)
  - Morgan, J.P., 1936-43 (Box 8, Folder 332)
  - Morris, Harrison S., 1931-44 (Box 8, Folder 333)
  - Mowbray, H. Siddons, 1904-54 (Box 8, Folder 334)
  - "N" general, 1895-1953, n.d. (Box 9, Folder 335)
    Nankivell, Frank A.
    Nash, William G.
    Nevins, Allan
    Nichols, S.B.
    Nicholson, D.
    North, A.T.
  - Nichols, Hobart, 1923-27 (Box 9, Folder 336)
  - Norton, Ray, n.d. (Box 9, Folder 337)
  - "O" general, 1920-41, n.d. (Box 9, Folder 338)
    Oberhardt
    Obestuffer, George
    Ogden, H.W.
    Oppenheim, Amy S.
    Ortgies, William S., Mrs.
    Otis, E.
  - O'Connor, Andrew, 1910-27 (Box 9, Folder 339)
  - "P" general, 1901-54, n.d. (Box 9, Folder 340-342)
    Palmer, Stephen A.
    Parish, Stephen
    Park, John G.
    Parker, George F.
    Parsons, Harold Woodbury
    Pennypacker, Isaac R.
    Perrin, H.W.
    Perry, Walter Scott
    Phillips, Duncan
    Phillips, J.H.
    Pine, J.
    Players Club
    Polk, Elizabeth H.
    Polk, Frank
    Pope, Arthur W.
    Pottinger, David T.
    Pratt, A.G.
    Price, Frederic N.
    Proctor, A.
    Prixtly, E.
    Prixtly, George
    Pulitzer, Joseph
    Putnam, G.P
  - Painter, H. McM., 1920, n.d. (Box 9, Folder 343)
  - Parrish, Samuel L., 1924-28 (Box 9, Folder 344)
  - Parsons, Geoffrey, 1919-48 (Box 9, Folder 345)
  - Parsons, T.W., 1889-90 (Box 9, Folder 346)
  - Paton, David, 1918-23, n.d. (Box 9, Folder 347)
  - Paton, William Agnew, 1917-18 (Box 9, Folder 348)
  - Patten, William, 1930-33, n.d. (Box 9, Folder 349)
  - Pennell, Joseph and Elizabeth, 1922-35 (Box 9, Folder 350)
  - Perrine, Van Dering, 1925, n.d. (Box 9, Folder 351)
  - Perry, Lewis, 1943 (Box 9, Folder 352)
  - Platt, Charles A., 1913-33, n.d. (Box 9, Folder 353-354)
  - Pollock, Walter Herries, 1901-04 (Box 9, Folder 355)
  - Pope, John Russell, 1911-41 (Box 9, Folder 356)
  - Price, Walter W., 1926-41 (Box 9, Folder 357)
  - Pyle, W. Scott, n.d. (Box 9, Folder 358)
  - "R" general, 1893-1942 (Box 9, Folder 359-361)
    Radin, Herman T.
    Rand, Ellen
    Rawson, Herbert
    Reasoner, David
    Reich, Jacques
    Reid, Wallace
    Reitz, L.
    Remington, Frederic
    Reyburn, S.W.
    Rhodes, Harrison
    Rice, G.
    Richards, C.P.
    Richter, Gisela M.A.
    Ricketts
    Rinehart & Company
    Robinson
    Robinson, Corinne Roosevelt
    Rockefeller, John D.
    Rodin, A.
    Roerich, N.
    Rofister, G.K.
    Rogers, G.V.
    Root, E.
    Rorimer, James J.
    Rosseau, Percival
    Rossiter, E.K.
    Roth, Frederick C.R.
    Russell, James J.
    Russell, T.H.
  - Reid, Helen (Rogers), 1919-53, n.d. (Box 9, Folder 362)
  - Reid, Elizabeth M., 1916-30, n.d. (Box 9, Folder 363)
  - Reid, Ogden, 1913-53 (Box 9, Folder 364)
  - Reid, Robert, 1897-1929, n.d. (Box 9, Folder 365)
  - Reid, Whitelaw, 1897-1912 (Box 9, Folder 366-371)
  - Reynolds, Jackson, 1931-37 (Box 9, Folder 372)
  - Rhoades, Katharine N., 1919-27 (Box 9, Folder 373)
  - Robinson, Edward, 1915-26 (Box 9, Folder 374)
  - Rogers, William A., 1919 (Box 9, Folder 375)
  - Roosevelt, Theodore, 1911-24 (Box 9, Folder 376)
  - "S" general, 1896-1951, n.d. (Box 10, Folder 377-382)
    Sachs, Paul
    Sackett, Henry W.
    Sartan, William
    Satterlee, Herbert L.
    Satties, Rollin
    Savage, Eugene
    Sawyer, Philip
    Schnakenberg, Henry
    Schock, Hiram
    Scudder, Janet
    Seaman, Owen
    Sears, C.
    Sears, Sarah
    Secker, C.
    Seeley, R.
    Seibert
    Seitz, Don C.
    Seward, F.
    Seymour, George D.
    Shaw, Lois
    Sheldon, Edward
    Shepard, Frederick J.
    Sherman, Frederic Fairchild
    Sherwood, H.F.
    Shifman, Ellen
    Shinn, Everett
    Shore, Henrietta M.
    Shreve, R.H.
    Shurtleff, Mrs. R.M.
    Shurtleff, Stella H.
    Silbert, Ben
    Simmons, Edward
    Simmons, Will
    Sizer, Theodore
    Smalley, George
    Smedley, Will Larymore
    Smith, Albert E., Mrs.
    Smith, Avery
    Smith, George
    Smith, Goldwin
    Smith, Joseph
    Smith, Marie
    Smith, Theodore Clarke
    Smith, William J.
    Sorine, S.
    Spalding, Mary Pyle
    Spencer, Herbert
    Spencer, Margaret F.
    Sperling, Harry G.
    Speyer, James
    "The Sphere"
    Squine, E.
    Starr, Sydney
    Starrett, Vincent
    Steele, Fletcher
    Steese, Edward
    Sterner, Albert
    Stetson, Francis L.
    Stewart, Mrs.
    Straight, Willard
    Strang, William
    Street, Julian
    Strong, Austen
    Stutfield, Hugh
    St. Ward, John
    Sullivan, Alice
    Sullivan, Mark
    Sulzberger, Arthur Hays
    Symonds, Margaret
    Symons, Arthur
  - Sabin, Pauline, 1923, n.d. (Box 10, Folder 383)
  - Saint-Gaudens, Augustus, 1899-1953, n.d. (Box 10, Folder 384)
  - Saint-Gaudens, Homer, 1907-53 (Box 10, Folder 385)
  - Sawyer, G.P., 1918-19 (Box 10, Folder 386-389)
  - Scribner, Arthur, 1907-40 (Box 10, Folder 390-391)
  - Sedgwick, Ellery Sedgwick, Henry Sedgwick, Theodore, 1938-44 (Box 10, Folder 392)
  - Selincourt, Basil, 1944, n.d. (Box 10, Folder 393)
  - Sert, ---, 1932-38, n.d. (Box 10, Folder 394)
  - Sherman, Stuart Pratt, 1924-25 (Box 10, Folder 395)
  - "Silvercruys", 1927 (Box 10, Folder 396)
  - Skinner, Otis (and Cornelia Otis), 1953, n.d. (Box 10, Folder 397)
  - Smith, F. Hopkinson, 1898-1911 (Box 10, Folder 398)
  - Speed, Harold, 1944-48 (Box 10, Folder 399)
  - Stedman, Edmund Clarence, 1891-1916 (Box 10, Folder 400-401)
  - Sterne, Maurice, 1927-39 (Box 10, Folder 402)
  - Stevenson, Robert Louis, 1882 (Box 10, Folder 403)
  - Stieglitz, Alfred, 1925-32 (Box 10, Folder 404)
  - Stokes, Anson Phelps, 1915 (Box 10, Folder 405)
  - "T" general, 1864-1942, n.d. (Box 10, Folder 406-407)
    Taft, Charles P.
    Taft, Mary H.
    Tanner, N.V.
    Tarbell, Edmund C.
    Taylor, Francis Henry
    Taylor, C.
    Taylor, D.
    Thanhouser, Edwin
    Thomas, A.E.
    Thomas, John W.
    Thomas, Lewis S.
    Thayer, Ethel R.
    Thayer, S.
    Thayer, W.R.
    Thorne, William
    Thurston, A.
    Tiffe, Mary P.
    Tittle, Walter
    Tolvay, Charles de
    Towne, Charly
    Tracy, Caroline S.
    Treidler, Adolph
    Trevelvan
    Trowbridge, Alexander, B.
    Tucker, Allen
    Turnbull, Lenore Young
    Turner, Helen M.
    Turner, Chauncy, Mrs.
  - Tack, Augustus Vincent, 1919-20 (Box 10, Folder 408)
  - Tarkington, Booth, 1927-43 (Box 10, Folder 409)
  - Tyler, Elisina Royall, 1937 (Box 10, Folder 410)
  - Ulreich, Edward B., n.d. (Box 10, Folder 411)
  - Updike, Daniel B., 1922-42 (Box 10, Folder 412)
  - "V" general, 1898-1932 (Box 10, Folder 413-414)
    Vail, Gertrude
    Valentiner, W.R.
    Van der Burch, Comte A.
    Van Doren, Irita
    Van Wyke, Henry
    Van Loon, Hendrik Willem
    Van Rensselaer, M.G.
    Vaughan, Malcolm
    Vedder, Elihu
    Vezin, Charles
    Vignauer, Henry
    Vinton, P.
    Vitale, Ferruccio
    Vollard, Ambrose
    Von Lossberg, W.F.
    Vormoh, R.
  - "W" general, 1882-1944, n.d. (Box 11, Folder 415-418)
    Walcott, Chester H.
    Waldo, Richard H.
    Walker, John
    Walker, Howard C.
    Walker, A. Stewart
    Wallace, Edna Kingsley
    Ward, Elizabeth
    Warren, Arthur
    Warren, Susan L.
    Watkins, S.C.G.
    Watterson, Henry
    Wave, William P.
    Weaver, Lawrence
    Weeks, John
    Weienkampf, Frank
    Welch, William H.
    Welcher, Emma Avery
    Wesleyan University
    West, Andrew A.
    Whelks, Elizabeth Stuart
    Whibler, Charles
    Whidder, W.
    Whigham, H.F.
    White, Bessie
    White, Henry
    White, Nelson
    White, Richard Grant
    Whiting, Frederic
    Whitney, C.
    Whitney, Gertrude
    Whitney, W.D.
    Whittemore, Julia S.
    Wickender, R.
    Wierum, Otto
    Wildenstein, Felix
    Wiles, Irving R.
    Williams, Chas S.
    Williams, Frederic A.
    Williams, J.K.
    Wilson, H.L.
    Wilstain, Paul
    Winlock, J.T.
    Winlock, Herbert E.
    Witt, Robert
    Wolff, WIlliam Almon
    Woolley, William H.
    Wright, Harold
    Wright, Henry J.
  - Ward, Sam, n.d. (Box 11, Folder 419)
  - Warner, Charles Dudley, 1879-88 (Box 11, Folder 420)
  - Weir, J. Alden, 1909-21 (Box 11, Folder 421)
  - Wharton, Edith, 1915-37 (Box 11, Folder 422)
  - Whistler, James McNeill, 1899-1925, n.d. (Box 11, Folder 423)
    Includes material about Whistler
    and a draft talk by Cortissoz
  - White, Lawrence Grant, 1889-1934 (Box 11, Folder 424)
  - Whitman, Walt, n.d. (Box 11, Folder 425)
  - Wilson, Francis, 1914-23 (Box 11, Folder 426)
  - Winter, William (auto-bibliography), n.d. (Box 11, Folder 427)
  - Winter, William, 1881-1917, n.d. (Box 11, Folder 428-430)
    Includes photographs
  - Winter, William (letters to D. Nicholson), 1895-1902, n.d. (Box 11, Folder 431)
  - Winthrop, Grenville L., 1928-54 (Box 11, Folder 432)
  - Wister, Owen, 1858-1935, n.d. (Box 11, Folder 433)
  - Woolf, S. J., 1930, n.d. (Box 11, Folder 434)
  - Wormeley, Katharine P., 1893-1953, n.d. (Box 11, Folder 435-438)
  - Wormeley, Katharine P. (misc. letters to), 1899-1907 (Box 12, Folder 439-444)
  - Wormeley, Katharine P. (to Nicholson), n.d. (Box 12, Folder 445)
  - "Y" general, 1921-28 (Box 12, Folder 446)
    Yarrow, Sharian
    Yashiro, Yuki
    York, Muriel
    Young, C.
    Young, M.
  - Young, Owen D., 1929-53 (Box 12, Folder 447)
  - Ziegler, Edward, 1921-23 (Box 12, Folder 448)
  - Zigrosser, Carl, 1943 (Box 12, Folder 449)
- Printed Material, 1883-1955; Series II; 0.4; (1 box)
  Series II, Printed Material, is arranged in five
  alphabetically listed subseries.
  - ADDRESSES BY CORTISSOZ
    - Address on John Singer Sargent, 1907 (Box 13, Folder 450)
    - American Institute of Architects Address, 1923 May 18 (Box 13, Folder 451)
    - Andover Commencement Address, 1934 (Box 13, Folder 452)
    - Henry Bacon Memorial Dedication Address, 1926 Nov 28 (Box 13, Folder 453)
    - Herald Tribune Conferences on Current Problems, 1935, n.d. (Box 13, Folder 454)
  - ARTICLES BY CORTISSOZ
    - "The Apotheosis of Whitman", n.d. (Box 13, Folder 455)
    - "Cass Gilbert", 1934 Jul (Box 13, Folder 456)
    - "Charles A. Platt", n.d. (Box 13, Folder 457)
    - "The Death of Henrik Ibsen", n.d. (Box 13, Folder 458)
    - "Dutch Life in Old Dutch Paintings", 1942 Oct 11 (Box 13, Folder 459)
    - "Edward Burne-Jones", n.d. (Box 13, Folder 460)
    - "Fifty Years of Art Criticism", 1941 Oct 5 (Box 13, Folder 461)
    - "George Bellows in his Draughtsmanship", 1936 Oct 4 (Box 13, Folder 462)
    - "A Group of French Impressionists", 1940 Mar 31 (Box 13, Folder 463)
    - "Henri Rochefort", 1913 Jul 3 (Box 13, Folder 464)
    - "Henry Bacon", n.d. (Box 13, Folder 465)
    - "Lydenberg as a Friend", 1943 (Box 13, Folder 466)
    - "Mrs. Augustus Saint-Gaudens", 1926 Jul 8 (Box 13, Folder 467)
    - "The Origins of Our Landscape Art", 1944 Apr 23 (Box 13, Folder 468)
    - "The Painting and Sculpture of Japan", 1936 Sep 27 (Box 13, Folder 469)
    - "Some Incidents Ushering in 1943", 1943 Jan 10 (Box 13, Folder 470)
    - "Stanford White", 1906 Jul 25 (Box 13, Folder 471)
    - "What I Think of the New Ball", 1931 Jul (Box 13, Folder 472)
    - "Whistler, James Abbott McNeill", n.d. (Box 13, Folder 473)
  - BOOK REVIEWS BY CORTISSOZ
    - The American Artist and His Times, by Homer Saint-Gaudens, 1943 Nov 23 (Box 13, Folder 474)
    - The American Leonardo: A Life of Samuel F. B. Morse, by Carleton Mabee, 1943 Feb 14 (Box 13, Folder 475)
    - The Athenaeum Gallery, by Mabel Munson Swan, 1941 Jul 27 (Box 13, Folder 476)
    - A Biography of William Cullen Bryant, with Extracts from his Private Correspondence, by Parke Godwin, [1883] (Box 13, Folder 477)
    - John Quincy Adams, by John T. Morse, [1898] (Box 13, Folder 478)
    - Oliver Wendell Holmes, Poet, Litterateur, Scientist, by William Sloane Kennedy, [1883] (Box 13, Folder 479)
  - ARTICLES ABOUT CORTISSOZ
    - General articles, 1930-51, n.d. (Box 13, Folder 480)
    - Fiftieth anniversary notices and tributes, 1948 Oct-Dec (Box 13, Folder 481)
    - The Life of Whitelaw Reid: review, 1921 Jun 4 (Box 13, Folder 482)
    - Obituaries, 1948 Oct (Box 13, Folder 483)
  - OTHER PRINTED MATERIAL
    - Catalogue of the Abbott H. Thayer Memorial Collection, 1922 (Box 13, Folder 484)
    - Dinner invitation and menu, 1937, 1941 (Box 13, Folder 485)
    - Lectures at the Metropolitan Museum of Art: Poster, 1925-26
    - Memorial tribute to Chester Aldrich, [1941] (Box 13, Folder 486)
    - Memorial tribute to Stanford White, 1921 Dec 10 (Box 13, Folder 487)
    - Program for the Dedication of the Lincoln Memorial, 1922 May
    - Program for "Reception to Mr. Josef Hofmann", 1925 Jan 11
      Signed by: Josef Hofmann, Sergei
      Rachmaninoff, Fritz Kreisler, blank
      blank, Alexander Siloti, Rubin
      Goldmark, Igor Stravinsky,
      Walter Damrosch
- Oversize
  Oversize material is housed in series order.
  - Honors and Certificates (Series I), 1925-38 (Box 14, Folder 488)
  - Lectures at the Metropolitan Museum of Art: Poster (Series II), 1925-26 (Box 14, Folder 489)
  - Program for the Dedication of the Lincoln Memorial (Series II), 1922 May (Box 14, Folder 490)
  - Program for "Reception to Mr. Josef Hofmann" (Series II), 1925 Jan 11 (Box 14, Folder 491)
- Restricted Fragile
  Conditions Governing Access
  Restricted fragile material. Reference surrogates have been substituted in the main files. For further information consult the appropriate curator.
  - Box 1, folder 3 (Box 15, Folder 492)
  - Box 1, folder 22 (Box 15, Folder 493)
  - Box 1, folder 23 (Box 15, Folder 494)
  - Box 1, folder 25 (Box 15, Folder 495)
  - Box 2, folder 37 (Box 15, Folder 496)
  - Box 2, folder 44 (Box 15, Folder 497)
  - Box 2, folder 65 (Box 15, Folder 498)
  - Box 2, folder 65 (Box 15, Folder 499)
  - Box 2, folder 71 (Box 15, Folder 500)
  - Box 2, folder 73 (Box 15, Folder 501)
  - Box 3, folder 74 (Box 15, Folder 502)
  - Box 3, folder 88 (Box 15, Folder 503)
  - Box 3, folder 6 (Box 15, Folder 504)
  - Box 3, folder 115 (Box 15, Folder 505)
  - Box 3, folder 116 (Box 15, Folder 506)
  - Box 4, folder 131 (Box 15, Folder 507)
  - Box 4, folder 152 (Box 15, Folder 508)
  - Box 4, folder 154 (Box 15, Folder 509)
  - Box 4, folder 165 (Box 15, Folder 510)
  - Box 4, folder 167 (Box 15, Folder 511)
  - Box 5, folder 171 (Box 15, Folder 512)
  - Box 5, folder 172 (Box 15, Folder 513)
  - Box 5, folder 181 (Box 15, Folder 514)
  - Box 5, folder 198 (Box 15, Folder 515)
  - Box 5, folder 198 (Box 15, Folder 516)
  - Box 5, folder 203 (Box 15, Folder 517)
  - Box 5, folder 204 (Box 15, Folder 518)
  - Box 5, folder 209 (Box 15, Folder 519)
  - Box 5, folder 213 (Box 15, Folder 520)
  - Box 6, folder 222 (Box 15, Folder 521)
  - Box 6, folder 229 (Box 15, Folder 522)
  - Box 6, folder 232 (Box 15, Folder 523)
  - Box 6, folder 247 (Box 15, Folder 524)
  - Box 6, folder 250 (Box 15, Folder 525)
  - Box 6, folder 265 (Box 15, Folder 526)
  - Box 7, folder 267 (Box 15, Folder 527)
  - Box 7, folder 278 (Box 15, Folder 528)
  - Box 7, folder 279 (Box 15, Folder 529)
  - Box 7, folder 280 (Box 15, Folder 530)
  - Box 7, folder 282 (Box 15, Folder 531)
  - Box 8, folder 292 (Box 15, Folder 532)
  - Box 8, folder 302 (Box 15, Folder 533)
  - Box 8, folder 303 (Box 15, Folder 534)
  - Box 8, folder 304 (Box 15, Folder 535)
  - Box 8, folder 312 (Box 15, Folder 536)
  - Box 8, folder 321 (Box 15, Folder 537)
  - Box 8, folder 328 (Box 15, Folder 538)
  - Box 8, folder 329 (Box 15, Folder 539)
  - Box 8, folder 331 (Box 15, Folder 540)
  - Box 8, folder 332 (Box 15, Folder 541)
  - Box 8, folder 334 (Box 15, Folder 542)
  - Box 9, folder 347 (Box 15, Folder 543)
  - Box 9, folder 351 (Box 15, Folder 544)
  - Box 9, folder 354 (Box 15, Folder 545)
  - Box 9, folder 367 (Box 15, Folder 546)
  - Box 9, folder 372 (Box 15, Folder 547)
  - Box 9, folder 375 (Box 15, Folder 548)
  - Box 9, folder 376 (Box 15, Folder 549)
  - Box 10, folder 377 (Box 15, Folder 550)
  - Box 10, folder 378 (Box 15, Folder 551)
  - Box 10, folder 379 (Box 15, Folder 552)
  - Box 10, folder 382 (Box 15, Folder 553)
  - Box 10, folder 384 (Box 15, Folder 554)
  - Box 10, folder 386 (Box 15, Folder 555)
  - Box 10, folder 389 (Box 15, Folder 556)
  - Box 10, folder 394 (Box 15, Folder 557)
  - Box 10, folder 398 (Box 15, Folder 558)
  - Box 10, folder 400 (Box 15, Folder 559)
  - Box 10, folder 401 (Box 15, Folder 560)
  - Box 10, folder 407 (Box 15, Folder 561)
  - Box 10, folder 411 (Box 15, Folder 562)
  - Box 10, folder 413 (Box 15, Folder 563)
  - Box 10, folder 414 (Box 15, Folder 564)
  - Box 11, folder 415 (Box 15, Folder 565)
  - Box 11, folder 416 (Box 15, Folder 566)
  - Box 11, folder 417 (Box 15, Folder 567)
  - Box 11, folder 421 (Box 15, Folder 568)
  - Box 11, folder 422 (Box 15, Folder 569)
  - Box 11, folder 423 (Box 15, Folder 570)
  - Box 11, folder 427 (Box 15, Folder 571)
  - Box 11, folder 428 (Box 15, Folder 572)
  - Box 11, folder 429 (Box 15, Folder 573)
  - Box 11, folder 430 (Box 15, Folder 574)
  - Box 11, folder 431 (Box 15, Folder 575)
  - Box 11, folder 434 (Box 15, Folder 576)
  - Box 11, folder 438 (Box 15, Folder 577)
  - Box 12, folder 439 (Box 15, Folder 578)
  - Box 12, folder 440 (Box 15, Folder 579)
  - Box 12, folder 445 (Box 15, Folder 580)
  - Box 12, folder 445 (Box 15, Folder 581)
  - Box 12, folder 446 (Box 15, Folder 582)
  - Box 13, folder 455 (Box 16, Folder 583)
  - Box 13, folder 458 (Box 16, Folder 584)
  - Box 13, folder 459 (Box 16, Folder 585)
  - Box 13, folder 461 (Box 16, Folder 586)
  - Box 13, folder 462 (Box 16, Folder 587)
  - Box 13, folder 463 (Box 16, Folder 588)
  - Box 13, folder 464 (Box 16, Folder 589)
  - Box 13, folder 466 (Box 16, Folder 590)
  - Box 13, folder 467 (Box 16, Folder 591)
  - Box 13, folder 468 (Box 16, Folder 592)
  - Box 13, folder 469 (Box 16, Folder 593)
  - Box 13, folder 470 (Box 16, Folder 594)
  - Box 13, folder 471 (Box 16, Folder 595)
  - Box 13, folder 474 (Box 16, Folder 596)
  - Box 13, folder 475 (Box 16, Folder 597)
  - Box 13, folder 476 (Box 16, Folder 598)
  - Box 13, folder 477 (Box 16, Folder 599)
  - Box 13, folder 478 (Box 16, Folder 600)
  - Box 13, folder 479 (Box 16, Folder 601)
  - Box 13, folder 480 (Box 16, Folder 602)
  - Box 13, folder 481 (Box 16, Folder 603)
  - Box 13, folder 482 (Box 16, Folder 604)